sustainablepersonalfinance.com 2014-12-23

# Privacy - Sustainable Personal Finance

**Your Privacy**  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

 **Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html> Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, Sustainable Personal Finance has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

 **Collection of non-personally-identifiable information by third parties** – Third parties (including advertising services) may be placing and reading cookies on your browser in the normal course of providing services to this website. Some services on this site also may use web beacons (tiny small transparent images) to collect information in the course of providing services to this website. Your web browser should have options to manage cookies should this be desirable. Consult your browser’s help section for information on viewing, setting, and changing these options. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information ( _not_ including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

**E-mail Subscriptions** – This website’s feed services collect the e-mail addresses of individuals that subscribe to our RSS feed via e-mail. Individual information about subscribers to this website’s feed is held in strict confidence; we will not release or disclose any specific subscriber information under any circumstances, unless required by law. Aggregated information stripped of any personally identifiable information may be disclosed.

 **Web Server Traffic** – This website records information about how people access this website. This includes things such as your IP address (or DNS), your browser, and your operating system. We do not and will not use this information to track down any personally identifiable information about you, unless required by law.

 **Comments** – Comments submitted to this website are the responsibility of the commenter. We reserve the right to remove or edit comments at our discretion. Site URLs (if provided) are published along with comments. E-mail addresses are required with the submission of comments but are not disclosed, unless the commenter deliberately does so him/herself by entering the e-mail address in the main comment box in addition to the box clearly labeled for the e-mail address.

 **E-mail** – E-mail sent to the site either through the contact form or directly to the owner in connection with this site is considered property of this site, and questions or tips may be published at the owner’s option. In such cases, this website will not disclose any personally identifying information, unless required to by law.

 **External Links** – The web site contains links to other websites not owned by the owner of this website. We will not, and cannot, control how your personal information is used on these other websites. Consult the privacy policies of the linked websites to see how they use your information.

 **Changes to this Privacy Statement**  
The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of Sustainable Personal Finance then you may contact us.

 **Disclaimer for** **http://sustainablepersonalfinance.com**

The information contained within SustainablePersonalFinance.com is for general information and does not constitute professional financial advice. The contents represent individual opinions (although, they are usually well-informed and logical). Any information you use from this site is used entirely at your own risk, and the site owners and operators specifically disclaim all warranties, express, implied or statutory, regarding the accuracy, timeliness, and/or completeness of the information contained herein, as well as its suitability to any particular need. Please [contact us](http://sustainablepersonalfinance.com/contact/) directly to schedule a consultation if you require advice regarding your specific situation.

 **Disclosure Policy for  [http://sustainablepersonalfinance.com](http://sustainablepersonalfinance.com/)**

This blog is a personal blog written and edited by the staff at Sustainable Personal Finance.. For questions about this blog, please contact  [sustainablepersonalfinance@gmail.com](mailto:sustainablepersonalfinance@gmail.com).

This blog accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, paid insertions or other forms of compensation.

The compensation received may influence the advertising content, topics or posts made in this blog. That content, advertising space or post may not always be identified as paid or sponsored content.

The owner(s) of this blog is compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics. Even though the owner(s) of this blog receives compensation for our posts or advertisements, we always give our honest opinions, findings, beliefs, or experiences on those topics or products. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely the bloggers’ own. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question.

This blog does not contain any content which might present a conflict of interest.

To get your own policy, go to http://www.disclosurepolicy.org

Thanks for visiting our site!
